const questions = [
{
	question: "What are the mascots for the 2018 Winter Olympic Games?",
	answer: {
		a: "Rabbit and Lion",
		b: "Dragon and Tiger",
		c: "Tiger and Bear",
		d: "Penguin and Seal"
	},
	correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
	question: "Where does the 2018 Winter Olympic takes its place?",
	answer: {
		a: "South Korea",
		b: "North Korea",
		c: "Both Koreas",
		d: "Russia"
	},
	correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
	question: "How many times have South Korea hosted Olympic games?",
	answer: {
		a: "One Winter Olympic",
		b: "Two Winter Olympics",
		c: "One Winter and Summer Olympics",
		d: "Two Winter and Two Summer Olympics"
	},
	correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
	question: "Which of following games are NOT playing in 2018 Winter Olympic?",
	answer: {
		a: "Skeleton",
		b: "Snowboarding",
		c: "Ice Hockey",
		d: "Sled Dog Racing"
	},
	correctAnswer: "d"
},
{
	question: "How many days do Winter Olympic Games run?",
	answer: {
		a: "14 days",
		b: "28 days",
		c: "16 days",
		d: "7 days"
	},
	correctAnswer: "c"
// },
// {
// 	question: "How many times has the hosting country, South Korea, ever won a medal in snow games?",
// 	answer: {
// 		a: "None (0)",
// 		b: "One (1)",
// 		c: "Seven (7)",
// 		d: "Twenty Two (22)"
// 	},
// 	correctAnswer: "a"
// },
// {
// 	question: "In year 2022, next Winter Olympic will be hosted from which contury?",
// 	answer: {
// 		a: "Japan",
// 		b: "Canada",
// 		c: "United States",
// 		d: "China"
// 	},
// 	correctAnswer: "d"
// },
// {
// 	question: "Pyoungchang 2018 Olympic games will include one (1) Puerto Rico athlete. Which game(s) will s/he play?",
// 	answer: {
// 		a: "Alpine skiing",
// 		b: "Bobsleigh",
// 		c: "Figure skating",
// 		d: "Speed skating"
// 	},
// 	correctAnswer: "a"
// },
// {
// 	question: "What is the official slogan for Winter Olympic?",
// 	answer: {
// 		a: "Celebration",
// 		b: "Passion, Connected",
// 		c: "Peace and Love",
// 		d: "Freinds Forever"
// 	},
// 	correctAnswer: "b"
// },
// {
// 	question: "Which games will feature unified South and North korea play?",
// 	answer: {
// 		a: "Biathlon",
// 		b: "Nordic Combined",
// 		c: "Curling",
// 		d: "Ice Hockey"
// 	},
// 	correctAnswer: "d"
}]